Your Majesty,
陛下
here is what you requested.
这是您要的那个东西
Thank you, Zenia.
辛苦妳了 洁妮亚
As long as this plan goes as planned,
只要这个计划顺利进行
the demon's dominance over the human realm
魔之眷属针对人界的统治
DEMON'S FAMILY: THE BEAUTIES
(魔之眷属 美女)
will advance significantly.
又能前进一大步了
(Level 1 Demon Lord and One Room Hero)
《Lv1魔王与独居废勇者》
(Episode 4: A New Challenge for the Hero) Look.
(#4 勇者的新挑战!) 快看
Be happy, Hero.
高兴点吧 勇者
I bring you good news.
朕带了喜讯给你
What is this? Let me see.
这是什么鬼 我看看
Demon's Family: The Beauties Portraits Collection.
"魔之眷属 美女肖像集"
I give it to you generously out of sympathy for you, you poor thing.
这是朕怜悯你这个可怜虫 大发慈悲送你的
Aren't you thankful for me?
还不感谢朕
What exactly are you talking about?
你到底在讲什么
You used to be very popular with the ladies.
你以前似乎颇受异性欢迎
But now you can't even find a girlfriend.
如今却连一个好对象都找不到
You don't have any female friends, do you?
身边没有女人吧
I am the female…
这里有女人啊
What? I don't need a girlfriend.
什么好对象 我才不需要女朋友
Don't give me that.
少来这套
Despite what you say, I get the impression that you are pretty lonely.
嘴上那么说 其实心里很寂寞吧
DEMON'S FAMILY: THE BEAUTIES PORTRAITS COLLECTION This is a collection of photos and personal information
(魔之眷属 美女肖像集) 这是从朕的部下之中挑选的
about beautiful women from among my subordinates.
优质美女的照片与个人资料
I asked Zenia to make it.
是朕请洁妮亚制作的
I can assist you in matching up with a girl you like.
挑个中意的女孩 朕就可以帮你撮合一下
How could I possibly fall in love with a demon?
我哪可能跟魔族恋爱啊
Why not?
为什么
Come on. After all, I am a man who killed countless demons ten years ago.
拜托 我好歹是在十年前 杀死无数魔族的男人
Wouldn't they mind?
难道对方不会在意吗
It's not a big deal.
什么嘛 那只是小事
You don't have to worry.
用不着担心
I have already said that we demons have seven lives.
朕之前也说过 我等魔之眷属拥有七条命
We don't particularly care about our own lives and deaths.
不会拘泥于自己的生死
That's not the point.
不是这个问题吧
Anyway, take a look at them first.
总之你先看一遍再说
Each of them is a good and versatile girl.
她们都是任谁都会喜爱的好女孩喔
NAME: ZENIA, JOB: SECRETARY
(名字 洁妮亚 职业 秘书官)
Why is it her as soon as I open it?
怎么一翻开就是这家伙
It seems that Zenia is also a bit interested.
看来洁妮亚不是毫无意思嘛
Did she take these pictures herself?
这些是她自己拍的吗
What is she thinking?
那家伙脑袋里在想什么
She must be making a pass at you.
一定是在对你示好
Take a good look.
仔细看看
I don't need a woman who chases me naked when she is drunk.
算了吧 发酒疯全裸追着我跑的女人有点…
She is a decent girl when she doesn't drink.
只要不喝酒 就是个正经的好女孩
I highly doubt if a decent person would dress like that.
我倒是很疑惑 正经的人会穿成这样吗
Alright, take a look at the other girls.
好啦 不然看看其他女孩啊
Take your pick. You are so enviable, you brat.
任君挑选耶 你这小子太令人羡慕啦
NAME: REBECCA JOB: CAPTAIN OF THE BEAST DEMON CORPS' SIXTH SQUAD
(名字 蕾贝卡) (职业 兽魔兵团第六队长)
Isn't this a pig?
这不是猪吗
What are you talking about?
乱讲什么
Rebecca is a Half-Orc swordswoman and Beast Demon Corps elite.
蕾贝卡可是半兽人族的刚剑士 还是兽魔兵团的菁英
How can you call her a pig?
怎么可以骂她是猪
Because she is a pig, a real pig.
因为真的是猪啊 完完全全就是猪
Rebecca is truly a nice girl.
蕾贝卡真的是一个好女孩耶
Her hands are very skillful, too.
手也很灵巧
Look carefully.
看好了
Her favorite armor is also handcrafted by her.
她爱用的铠甲也是自己亲手打造的
Her femininity is quite amazing, isn't it?
女子力很惊人吧
She is so talented.
太猛了
No, the fact that she made her own armor goes far beyond the bounds of femininity.
不对 自制铠甲 早就超出了女子力的范畴吧
This person seems quite normal.
这个感觉倒是挺正常的
NAME: DESDALE Desdale, huh? You have good taste.
(名字 黛丝妲尔) 黛丝妲尔吗 你真有眼光
JOB: FIRST-CLASS SOLDIER IN THE MAGIC CORPS She is an intelligent and proficient magic warrior.
(职业 魔法兵团一等兵) 她是既聪明又精通魔法的优秀战士
Her temperament is a little slothful, but some find it endearing.
散发慵懒的气质 不过有人说这样更有魅力
In hand-to-hand combat, she entwines her opponent with her lower body.
还具有武斗派的一面 在肉搏战蜷曲下半身缠紧对手
Why aren't there any normal ones? Damn it.
怎么这样啦 可恶
Don't judge her by her appearance. I remember her hobby being sports.
别看她这样 朕记得她的兴趣是运动
A girl who loves sports is charming, isn't she?
爱运动的女孩子是不是魅力十足
That's not the point. The point is why she's a snake.
那不是重点 为什么她是蛇
Wouldn't it be great if she were human?
当个人类不好吗
What about this girl?
那这个女孩呢
NAME: YVON, JOB: SERVICE STAFF From head to toe, she's human.
(名字 伊冯 职业 服务人员) 从头到脚都是人类喔
You should say she used to be" human."
是"曾经"是个人类吧
Don't call this dead person a human.
不准把这种状态的生物叫做人类
Aren't you being too picky?
你未免太挑剔了吧
Darn it.
可恶
Look, there are so many options.
你看 有这么多人选
You'll definitely find a woman that suits your preferences.
肯定找得到符合你喜好的女性吧
I remember this giant dragon and squid.
我记得这只巨龙跟乌贼
After all, they're incredibly strong.
毕竟她们强得不得了
So, they are actually female.
话说回来 原来她们是母的
What do you expect me to do when you introduce them to me?
介绍她们给我 我也不能怎么样
So, which girl do you like?
所以呢 你看上了哪个女孩吗
Nobody, idiot.
完全没有 蠢蛋
Isn't this just a demon encyclopedia?
这只是魔物图鉴吧
Geez, your standards are so high.
真是的 动不动要求那么高
Tell me about the type of girl you prefer.
说来说去 你到底喜欢哪种类型的女生
Although telling you probably won't help,
虽然告诉你八成也没用
the essential condition is that she looks like a human.
不过必要条件是外观像个人类
You mean having hands and legs and moving on two feet?
意思是有手有脚 以双脚移动
Yes, that's right.
没错
How about a detachable head?
头部是可拆式也可以吗
Absolutely not, idiot.
绝对不要 蠢蛋
In that case, Zenia seems like a good candidate.
既然如此 洁妮亚算是个不错的人选吧
I don't like silly girls like her.
我不喜欢像她那样的傻妞
It's better if she's a bit smarter.
最好要聪明一点
What else?
还有什么
A decisive and forthright personality.
个性果断直爽
Excellent cooking skills, beautiful appearance,
厨艺高超 长得漂亮
a good figure and long, flowing black hair.
身材好 留着一头飘逸黑直发
With that, I would have no complaints.
这样就无可挑剔了
You have such high standards.
都不想想自己几两重
In that case, within my army…
这样的话 在军队中…
Transfigure.
变身
Look. What do you think, Hero?
看吧 如何啊 勇者
This is my disguise to avoid drawing human attention.
这是朕用来避人耳目的伪装
Take a look at my lustrous, flowing black hair and my hot body.
快看这头乌黑亮丽的飘逸长发 以及火热身材
It just so happens to be your ideal type.
正巧就是你的理想类型
And as you know,
而且如你所知
I can cook, clean, and do laundry. I'm like a virtuous wife and good mother.
煮饭 洗衣服 打扫都难不倒朕 可谓贤妻良母
Of course, the personality is faithful, decisive and forthright.
性格当然也是表里如一又果断直爽
It's really troublesome.
真是头疼呢
We are mortal enemies after all.
朕和你明明是宿敌
But if we were to get married,
不过假如我们结婚了
I would have a powerful intermediary in the human realm.
朕在人界就多了强力的管道
I'm just teasing you…
逗你的啦…
I-Is that Zenia?
是…是洁妮亚吗
Coming, I will open the door now.
来了 朕马上开门
Thank you, Your Majesty.
辛苦您了 陛下
What's wrong? Your cheeks are all red.
您怎么了 脸颊红通通的
Could it be that you caught a cold?
莫非是感冒了
No, I'm not blushing!
没有啦 没有脸红啦
Don't worry, I'm perfectly fine.
妳放心 朕好得很
Hero, do you want to become my subordinate?
勇者啊 要不要成为朕的部下
In doing so, you would also have seven lives.
这么一来 你也能拥有七条命
Why not enjoy eternal life with me?
何不与朕一同享受永恒的生命
Are you kidding me?
开什么玩笑
To abandon my human dignity and become a demon,
要我舍弃人类的尊严成为魔族
I'd rather die here.
我宁愿死在这里
That's really a shame.
真是太遗憾了
Then, fall into the oblivion of death.
那你就陷入死之忘却吧
Hero, do you want to become my subordinate?
勇者啊 要不要成为朕的部下
Reincarnate as a demon and gain power.
转生为魔之眷属 获得"力量"吧
That way, you would also have seven lives.
你也能拥有七条命
Didn't you ask me this ten years ago?
这不是十年前就问过了吗
Yes, I did.
是啊
I knew back then that you would refuse my invitation.
当时早已料到你会拒绝朕的邀请
But what about now?
不过现在意下如何
Are you an idiot?
蠢毙了
I'm serious.
朕是认真的
No way…
不可能…
If you want to talk nonsense, please do it in your dreams.
要讲梦话拜托去梦里讲
Don't prejudge and dismiss us.
不要不由分说全盘否定啦
At least listen to what I have to say.
至少听听看朕怎么说吧
Why are you so persistent about this matter?
你怎么异常坚持
DEMON FAMILY, REINCARNATION SEMINAR Come on, join the demon.
(魔之眷属 转生说明会) 来吧 你也加入魔之眷属吧
Reincarnation Seminar?
转生说明会
What's with this highly suspicious seminar?
这个可疑至极的讲座是怎样
What are the benefits of no longer being human and reincarnating as a demon?
不当人类 转生当魔之眷属会有哪些福利
Today, I will specially explain it to you.
今天朕来特别解释给你听
Let us start with the first perk.
首先是第一个福利 不管怎么说
WELL-KNOWN FOR ITS HIGH SALARY The pay is very high.
(赚高薪 吃得开) 就是薪水超高
Do you start out by talking about money?
一开始就谈钱吗
Didn't Fred say it before?
弗雷德不是说过吗
You don't have much left in your savings.
你的存款所剩不多了
You will be financially secure if you work for me.
只要当朕的部下就不愁没钱花
But I still have some savings.
但我还是有那么一点积蓄
After all, I used to earn a lot.
毕竟以前赚很多
I won't be out of money for food tomorrow.
不至于明天就没钱吃饭
Regardless of tomorrow or the day after,
先不论明天或后天
what about after ten or twenty years?
十年或二十年后你要怎么办
It's none of your business.
要你管
By then, I'll be dead. It doesn't matter.
到时我早就死了 不要紧啦
You are saying this again.
来了…又来这套
People who say such things won't shed a tear until they see the coffin.
偏偏讲这种话的人 就是不见棺材不掉泪
Yes, your thoughts are too simple.
没错 思考太肤浅了
Assuming you work at my castle,
假设来朕的城堡任职
your starting salary is 480 000 yen per month,
起薪是实质月薪48万日圆
with a bonus paid twice a year,
每年发两次奖金
a guaranteed salary increase and promotion, and pension benefits.
保证加薪升职 还有给付退休金
Of course, this is the salary of a general soldier.
当然啦 这是以一般士兵而论
Given your exceptional abilities and experience,
考虑到你具有卓越的实力与资历
it will at least triple this.
起码会是这个的三倍
Wait, what did you say?
等一下 你在说什么
Do you think it's not enough?
还不够吗
What about 2.5 million yen, which is five times the amount?
那就算五倍的250万日圆 如何
Are you serious?
你是认真的吗
People in the human realm are going to be so mad.
人类社会人士要气死了
Hold on, Your Majesty.
且慢 陛下
No amount of money can buy happiness without regular work breaks.
有再多的收入 没有休假 就无法经营多采多姿的生活
You don't have to worry about this.
用不着担心
REASONABLE WORK SCHEDULE, NO OVERTIME, FOUR DAYS OFF PER WEEK All demons are protected and have a comfortable working environment.
(合情合理的劳动规划) (至多工作五小时 不须加班) (完全周休四日制 强制请完特休) 我等魔之眷属都受到保障 有舒适的劳动环境
A maximum of five hours of work per day.
一天最多工作五小时
No overtime required.
当然不需要加班
Four days off every week.
每周完整休息四天
Four days off every week?
周休四天
It's really great.
实在是太棒了
You will not only be able to maintain your private time,
不但能够保有私人时间
but you will also have so much free time that you will be at a loss for what to do.
甚至会闲到不知道要干什么
Is this a privilege of castle staff?
这是城堡职员的特权吗
No, I can't be unfair.
不是啊 做事不能这么不平等
Private and government employees are treated equally.
无论是民间企业或公务员 一律比照办理
This is the right that demons should enjoy.
这是魔之眷属应享的权利
Can society function like this?
这样社会有办法运转吗
Of course, it can function, with ease.
当然可以运转 轻轻松松
Hold on, Your Majesty.
且慢 陛下
Will work lose its meaning
福利制度不够完善的话
if the welfare system is not comprehensive enough?
不就少了工作的意义吗
Of course, our welfare system is comprehensive.
福利制度当然也是一应俱全
We guarantee you a house in Jokamachi or the residential area.
保证能住在城下町 或是城内居住区的房子
We have clear provisions for license assistance, maternity, and parental leave.
辅助考取证照 生产育儿休假 皆有明文规定保障
Several other systems are in place to fully support my subordinates.
还有各式各样的制度 全面支持朕的部下
So you guys can have children, huh?
原来你们会生孩子喔
What else? Oh ya.
还有什么…对了
BODY, BRAIN, MAGICAL POWER A strong body that doesn't get sick,
(肉体 头脑 魔力) 不会得病的强健肉体
a brain that doesn't age,
不会衰老的头脑
BODY, BRAIN, MAGICAL POWER an endless supply of magical power,
(肉体 头脑 魔力) 再加上源源不绝的魔力
and an immortal soul that can be resurrected by sleeping.
以及死后沉睡 便能复活的永恒灵魂
UNDEAD BODY Don't skip over the most characteristic part of being a demon.
(不死之身) 不要草率带过最有魔族特色的部分
CONTRACT, AGREE TO BECOME A DEMON SIGN HERE
(契约书 同意成为魔之眷属) (在此署名)
As long as you become one of us,
只要成为我等的一员
you can escape all the troubles and insecurities of being human,
你便能摆脱人类的一切苦恼与不安
and the fear of death.
以及对于死亡的恐惧
YOU SHOULD JOIN
(就来当吧)
Come spend eternity with me,
何不与朕共度永恒的生命
Max.
麦克斯
I'm sorry.
抱歉
YOU SHOULD JOIN Let's just forget about this.
(你就当啦) 还是算了吧
Why?
为什么
Because you don't want to be my subordinate?
是因为不想当朕的部下吗
IS IT BAD TO BE A DEMON? Being a subordinate is just a formality.
(不好吗) 部下只是一个形式
We can maintain our current relationship.
我们可以维持现在这种关系
Or is it because of what you said ten years ago about "human dignity"?
还是因为十年前所说的 "人类的尊严"
Is "being human" that important to you?
"当一个人类" 对你来说有那么重要吗
What is this so-called human dignity?
人类的尊严是什么
Don't ask such a difficult question so bluntly.
不要直白地问那么难的问题
Didn't you say this yourself?
这不是你自己说的话吗
I was young and reckless back then.
当时年少轻狂
Even though I spoke with conviction, I was not sure what I was saying.
没头没脑 讲得煞有其事而已
I am no longer insisting on being "human."
如今我也没有坚持要 "当一个人类"
But how should I say this?
但是该怎么说
I can't easily give up "myself."
大概是因为 我无法轻易舍弃"做自己"
What does that mean?
什么意思
Even if you reincarnate, you won't lose your memory.
转生了也不会失去记忆啊
Becoming a demon means eternal life, wealth, and power.
成为魔族就能金钱与力量双收 还不会死
Then that "me" would no longer be me, but a different creature.
那我就不再是我 而是不同的生物了
Despite the fact that I was a very different person
虽然对十年前的我来说
than I was ten years ago.
现在的我也完全是另一个人了
And it is extremely inconvenient if I can't die.
而且死不了的话 实在不太方便
I can't bear the burden of an undead body.
不死之身令人承受不起啊
That's how it is for us humans.
对于人类来说就是如此
DO YOU REALLY NOT WANT TO BE A DEMON? Your suggestions are appreciated.
(真的不行吗) 感谢两位的提议
I must decline this invitation.
恕我拒绝这次的邀约
I…
朕…
I just wanted to be with you forever…
朕只是想跟你永远一起…
No, never mind.
不 没什么
It's such a pity, Your Majesty.
真是太遗憾了 陛下
WHAT A SHAME
(好可惜)
There's nothing we can do.
这也无可奈何
Max has seriously considered it.
麦克斯也认真考虑了一番
Mr. Max,
麦克斯先生
I'll keep the contract.
契约书我先留着
If you want to reincarnate, just let me know anytime.
想转生的话 随时跟我说一声
Is this contract so casual?
这种契约这么随意吗
But Hero,
但是勇者啊
since you've rejected my proposal,
既然你拒绝了朕的提案
you need to pull yourself together.
你就要自己学习重新振作
First, you need to plan your life.
首先要安排生活规划
You can't say anything like, "I'll die in ten years."
不准再说什么 "十年后就会死了"
Sorry, let me think…
抱歉 我想想…
Okay, I got it.
好 我知道了
I'll find a way to solve the money problem.
我会想办法解决钱的问题
You'll see.
走着瞧
I'll definitely earn several times the salary of the demon clan.
我一定会赚进魔族薪资的好几倍
BURNING WITH PASSION The Hero has regained his fighting spirit.
(熊熊燃烧) 勇者拿出斗志了
What is this thing?
这是什么东西
I'm going to make a video.
我要录像片
A video?
影片
I'll make a video and upload it to the internet to make money.
我要做影片上传到网络上赚钱
Such a difficult concept.
朕听不懂
Don't you know?
你不知道吗
This is called "Poocuber."
这个叫做" Poocuber"
The top people in it can earn over 100 million a year.
最顶尖的人 年收甚至可以高达一亿以上
A yearly income of 100 million? Are you serious?
居然有一亿 真的吗
Even if it doesn't reach that level,
就算不到那个境界
some videos of people yelling and playing games get millions of views.
有些影片只是玩游戏大吼大叫 观看次数也能达到一百万
With one view equaling one yen,
一次以一日圆来算
that is a million yen, making money is far too simple.
这样就能赚到一百万 实在太好赚了
Is it really that simple?
真的有那么简单吗
Alright, I'm starting now.
好 开工吧
What kind of video should I make? I guess I'll choose a game live stream.
要拍什么影片呢 果然是游戏实况吧
Is he alright?
没问题吗
ROOM 205 Mr. Max wants to be a Poocuber?
麦克斯先生要当Poocuber吗
Yeah, he just suddenly said it.
对啊 他昨天突然说的
It is not as easy as Your Majesty had been told.
那个行业没有听起来那么简单
You think so too, huh?
妳果然也是这么认为吗
How much can a regular Poocuber earn?
说来说去 一般来说Poocuber能赚多少钱
The Hero said one view equals one yen.
勇者说观看次数一次等于一日圆
MIKI That's impossible, I heard the price is even lower.
(密基) 那怎么可能 听说少多了
According to data, you can barely make a living
有数据显示 几乎天天上传 观看次数高达十万的影片
if you upload nearly every day and each video receives over 100,000 views.
也只能勉强温饱
Isn't that tough?
那不是很辛苦吗
This is not a job for the lazy.
懒惰的人做不来这行
To be honest, I don't think Mr. Max is the right fit for this.
老实说 麦克斯先生不太适合做这个
That's true,
话是这么说
but it's rare for him to show such enthusiasm.
但他难得拿出了干劲
Your Majesty, you spoil him too much.
陛下您太宠他了
You should give him a wake-up call.
应该要给他一记当头棒喝
But how should I put it?
可是…怎么说呢…
It's been a long time since I've seen the Hero so serious.
朕好久没看到勇者那么认真的模样
It's like he's back to the time when he fought against me ten years ago.
彷佛回到十年前与朕交锋的时候
Is it that exaggerated?
有那么夸张吗
How are you doing?
弄得如何
Don't talk to me right now.
现在不要跟我讲话
The microphone will pick up your voice!
会录到你的声音啦
I'm sorry.
对不起
Do you think the views will reach a million?
观看次数会不会有一百万
It's impossible to get that many from the start.
不可能一开始就那么多啦
I'm just starting out.
我才刚起步耶
What if it really reaches a million?
那如果成功了呢
Of course…
当然是…
What's wrong?
怎么了
The video…
影片…
FIRST GAME LIVE STREAM, FUN FREE GAME No one is watching…
(第一次游戏实况) (神乎其技 好玩的免费小游戏) 完全没人看
What kind of video did you make? Let me see.
你做了什么样的影片 让朕看看
Stop it! Don't look! It's so embarrassing.
住手 不准看 很丢脸耶
You idiot.
蠢蛋
Haven't you already made it public for the whole world to see?
不是早就公开给全世界看了吗
Let me take a look.
朕看看喔
Click here to watch, right?
这样就能观看了吗
SUPER INVINCIBLE FANTASY WORLD It's starting.
(超级无敌霹雳幻想世界) 开始了
Hello, uh…
大家好 呃
I'm Poocuber Mackie.
我是Poocuber麦奇
That's your voice!
是你的声音耶
And you even named yourself Mackie.
还取名叫麦奇
Stop nagging.
少啰嗦
Uh, this time, I'm playing a game…
呃 我这次啊 游戏…
A small game… a free small game...
小游戏…免费小游戏…
That's the theme I want to introduce.
就是要玩…要介绍的主题
-So, what about me? -Why are you mumbling and listless?
-那么 至于我呢 -口齿不清 讲个不停
-It's my first time… -Can't you speak more clearly?
-这是我第一次… -讲话怎么不讲清楚一点
My name is Mackie… and I will keep uploading videos.
我名叫麦奇 以后会继续…预计继续上传影片
Uh, this is my first video.
呃 这支影片啊 是我第一支影片
From now on, please saport me…
今后还请大家多多干燥
Saport? What are you talking about?
多多干燥
This is the title screen.
这就是标题画面
The title's text…
标题的文字…
Ah, you can see the game title.
啊 可以看到标志
And below it, there's "Start New Game," "Continue Playing", and "Exit".
然后下面是 "开始新游戏 继续游玩 退出"
Hurry up and start.
快点开始啦
Let's immediately choose "Exit."
那我们马上来选"退出"
I'm just kidding, it should be "Start New Game," haha.
开玩笑的啦 应该是"开始新游戏"才对
-Let's get started right away. -Finally starting.
-那就赶快开始吧 -终于开始了
I see, so this is how to defeat enemies.
原来如此 像这样打倒敌人
One after another, not bad.
一个接一个 真不错
Watch me defeating enemies like this.
殴啦殴啦殴啦 像这样打败敌人
And then we move forward, watch me…
然后前进 殴啦…
More enemies appearing, watch me…
又有敌人 殴啦…
Watch me…
殴啦…
Enemies show up again, watch me…
又出现啦 殴啦…
Nice. Hey, watch me.
好耶 嘿 殴啦
You're running out of things to say, aren't you?
没有其他可说的了
It's the Demon King! The Demon King! It's the Demon King!
是魔王耶 魔王 是魔王喔
Alright, let's defeat him.
好 打倒他吧
This is excited! Watch me…
热血沸腾耶 殴啦…
Darn it, I'm not going to lose. Watch me…
可恶 谁会输啊 殴啦…
Watch me… Seagulls! It's funny, right?
殴啦 海鸥啦 好笑吧
14 VIEWS 14 views, huh?
观看次数14次
There are actually 14 people who watched this.
居然有14个人看了这种东西
Don't be discouraged, Hero.
不要泄气 勇者
You've been working hard, making videos late into the night.
你很努力了 半夜也在弄影片
That alone is impressive, don't you think?
光是这样就很厉害了 好吗
You're right. I can't be discouraged by such a small setback.
你说得没错 不能因为这点小事消沉
Since live streaming games didn't work out,
既然游戏实况行不通
I'll just make a new video.
做新影片就好了
I heard product review videos are quite popular.
听说商品介绍挺受欢迎的
I'll give it a try.
来试试看吧
Uh, I bought some traditional pastries today.
呃 我今天买了古早点心
I'll taste them and see which one is the best.
来吃吃看哪个最好吃
Uh, even though I can't show my face.
呃 虽然我不能露脸
DELICIOUS TRADITIONAL PASTRY TASTE TEST MACKIE TRIED MANY TRADITIONAL PASTRIES THIS TIME
(好吃 古早点心试吃比较) (麦奇 这次试吃了很多古早点心)
MY MOTHER CHASTISED ME FOR SKIPPING MEALS BECAUSE I LIKED TRADITIONAL PASTRY.
(以前就爱吃 甚至吃不下正餐) (常常被妈妈骂)
WHICH ONE DO YOU LIKE? COMMENT BELOW PLEASE SUBSCRIBE TO MY CHANNEL
(大家喜欢哪种 留言告诉我唷) (请订阅我的频道)
WHO WANTS TO WATCH AN OLD MAN EAT PASTRIES? SO DISGUSTING. All of them are delicious, and they are all ranked No. 1.
(吃得脏兮兮) (大叔吃古早点心 谁看得下去) 都很好吃 都是第一名
I noticed there's a Poocuber singer lately.
最近好像有Poocuber歌手
I'll try to debut as a singer too.
我也来歌手出道一下
COVERED "LOVE STARS" A love story as dazzling as the stars.
(翻唱了"LOVE STARS") 谈一场 宛如星星 亮晶晶的恋爱
BAD SINGING AND POOR SOUND QUALITY, DON'T UNDERESTIMATE SINGING Ahem…
(难听死了 音质也很差) (别小看唱歌)
Wait a moment…
等一下
THREE-EYED KING, I THINK YOUR SINGING IS NICE I'll sing it again…
(三眼王 这种讲话方式不太好) (我觉得唱得很好听啊) (麦奇先生加油 我支持你) 我再唱一次
Current event topics always have an audience.
时事题材不论何时都能吸引目光
THE REAL FACE OF REPUBLIC GAMMA BRINGS TEARS Let me make some easy money.
(刚玛共和国的真实样貌令人泛泪) 轻松大赚一笔
I'M A TERRORIST, THIS IS FAKE, RIGHT?
(我是恐怖分子 骗人的吧)
WHICH NEWS WEBSITE DID YOU COPY THIS FROM?
(从哪个新闻网站抄来的吧)
SUBTITLES APPEAR TOO SLOW AND ARE HARD TO READ PLEASE LEARN MORE ABOUT VIDEO PRODUCTION TECHNIQUES
(字幕太慢出现 难以阅读) (请多多学习影片制作方式)
THIS GARBAGE HAS FIVE ADS
(这种烂东西还塞了五个广告)
THREE-EYED KING, YOU'RE AMAZING I'VE NEVER HEARD OF THESE THINGS BEFORE
(三眼王 好厉害 都是第一次听说)
MR. MACKIE IS SO KNOWLEDGEABLE PLEASE KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK IN THE FUTURE
(麦奇先生真是博学多闻) (以后也要加油喔)
Anyway, I can't be a Poocuber.
我终究不是当Poocuber的料
This job is much harder than it looks.
这个职业比表面上看起来还难
It's okay if you want to give up.
要放弃也没关系
Don't force yourself to keep going.
不必逼自己硬撑下去
Darn it.
可恶…
Why not make one last video to try?
不然最后再拍一支影片试试看
Do your best to make it.
使出全身解数
If it's still not popular, you'll be more willing to give up.
若这样还是不受欢迎 你也比较容易放弃吧
I won't force you.
朕也不会强迫你
If necessary, I can help you too.
有必要的话 朕也能帮你
Really? Are you willing to help me?
真的吗 你愿意帮我吗
Of course.
当然
I can be the cameraman, I'll do anything.
摄影也可以 朕什么都做
LIVE STREAM STARTING SOON
(直播即将开始)
CURRENTLY STREAMING
(直播中)
Can you see me on the screen?
能在画面上看到朕吗
NO PROBLEM It seems like there's no issue.
(没问题) 看来没问题
Hello everyone, I'm the Three-eyed King.
大家好 朕是三眼王
Uh, today I want to try…
呃 朕今天想来试试看…
this thing called "live streaming."
这个叫做"直播"的东西
REMEMBER TO SMILE Will people really come to watch me?
(笑容) 真的会有人来看吗
Nice to meet you all.
总之请多多指教
HELLO, WHO ARE YOU? IT'S MY FIRST TIME WATCHING. YOUR WAY OF SPEAKING IS SO STRANGE.
(妳好 谁啊 我第一次看) (讲话方式好怪)
READ THE COMMENTS AND CHAT WITH THEM
(念留言做反应)
It seems quite a few people have come. How nice…
好像来了不少人 善哉…
My way of speaking?
朕的讲话方式吗
Is it that strange? Hahaha.
有那么奇怪吗
INTERESTING CHARACTER, STRONG PERSONALITY IS THAT A SCHOOL'S UNIFORM? A HIGH SCHOOL GIRL?
(角色定位不错 个性强烈) (那是水手服吗 是女高中生)
Are you talking about my outfit?
这身衣服吗
This is a school uniform.
这是学生服
That's right.
没错 这是水手服
It has a very human style…
很有人类的风格…
No, I mean, it's very friendly.
不对 风格很亲民吧
STAND UP, LET THEM SEE YOUR OUTFIT
(站起来介绍衣服)
Look.
你们看
This is just a normal school uniform, right?
怎么看 都是普通的学生服吧
THREE-EYED KING'S LIVE STREAM 2,045 PEOPLE ARE WATCHING
(三眼王的直播)
IS THIS OKAY? I CAN ALMOST SEE IT… I WANT TO SEE YOUR BODY, SO CUTE
(这没问题吗 要看到了…) (想看身体 可爱)
You said it's cute? I'm flattered.
可爱吗 真是难为情
SHOW MORE SKIN, YOUR SKIN IS SO NICE Everyone is commenting so actively.
(多露一点 皮肤真好) 大家留言这么踊跃
YOU'RE CHUBBY, THE UNIFORM IS GREAT
(真胖 制服就是赞)
This is quite fun.
还挺有意思的嘛
HAVE SOME POPSICLE
(冰)
That's right.
对了
He told me to have popsicle on the live stream.
他叫朕在直播吃这个…不对
No. I suddenly wanted to have some popsicle.
朕突然想吃冰
Alright, now I'm going to taste and review this popsicle.
好 那么朕要来试吃一下这支棒冰
Watch closely, everyone.
大家看好啰
Sweet and cold, so refreshing…
甜甜冰冰的 又清爽…
DON'T BITE WITH YOUR TEETH Sweet and cold, refreshing flavor…
(不要露出牙齿)
Why?
为什么
SUCH A DARING MOVE, LOOKS SO DELICIOUS 10,028 PEOPLE ARE WATCHING
(太猛了 看起来真好吃) (10,028人正在观看)
YOU'RE DOING GREAT
(很好)
Are there really so many people watching?
有这么多人都在看吗
Everyone's comments are so lively.
留言也很热络
Oh no, I accidentally dripped onto my clothes.
糟了 不小心滴下去了
I'm feeling hot anyway.
突然觉得好热
Might as well take it off.
干脆脱掉好了
IS THIS FOR REAL? AWESOME! IS THERE SOMEONE BEHIND YOU? BE CAREFUL NOT TO GET YOUR CHANNEL BANNED
(真假 赞啦 后面是不是有人) (小心频道被封锁)
THREE-EYED KING IS THE BEST, YOUR BELLY IS SO BEAUTIFUL YOU LOOK SO APPETIZING, YOUNG AND CUTE
(三眼王最棒 肚子好漂亮) (感觉真可口 年轻可爱)
FINALLY, HURRY UP AND UNDRESS… ALMOST THERE… READY FOR FULL NUDITY, YOUR SKIN IS SO NICE
(终于啊 快脱 要看到了…) (全裸待机 皮肤真好)
ABOUT TO BE BANNED, YOU'RE SO YOUNG WHO'S THAT BEHIND YOU? LUCKY TO BE ALIVE
(要被封锁了 好年轻) (后面那是谁 活着真好)
WILL FOLLOW YOU FOR A LIFETIME, AWESOME AND CUTE THANK YOU, KING, THE COLORS ARE SO BEAUTIFUL
(追随一辈子 赞啦 可爱) (谢谢王 颜色好漂亮)
GODDESS, I CAUGHT UP, YAY! AMAZING HOW TERRIFYING, THANKS FOR THE HOSPITALITY
(女神 赶上了 好耶 太棒了) (好可怕 谢谢招待)
SUBSCRIBED, SO BEAUTIFUL
(已订阅 好漂亮)
THIS ACCOUNT HAS VIOLATED POOCUBE'S TERMS OF USE.IT HAS BEEN SUSPENDED
(此账号违反PooCube使用规范) (已遭到停权)
VIOLATION: LIVESTREAMING OR UPLOADING IMMORAL CONTENT
(违反项目 直播或上传影片) (违反公序良俗)
We're such fools.
我们真是太傻了